<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="73">
    <author>SbSh / Frvetz</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>

    <title>
        <en>Random Fuels Prices For Diesel And AdBlue(DEF)</en>
        <de>Zufällige Preise Für Diesel Und AdBlue(DEF)</de>
    </title>

    <description>
        <de><![CDATA[Wie im realen Leben verändert sich immer wieder der Dieselpreis und hin und wieder auch der AdBlue(DEF) Preis.
Wenn man mal einen günstigen Preis an der Tankstelle hat, sollte man zuschlagen und seinen Tank am Hof füllen - es wird bestimmt wieder teurer.
Saison und Precision Farming Kompatibel. Für den realismus sollte bei Revamp die Korrektur der Einkaufspreise deaktiviert werden.
FS22_DefPack bitte die aktuelle Version mind. 1.0.0.1 aus dem Gitlab nehmen.

gitHub: https://github.com/s4t4n/FS22_RandomFuelsPrices]]></de>
        <en><![CDATA[As in real life, the price of diesel keeps changing, and every now and then the price of AdBlue (DEF) too.
If you ever get a cheap price at the gas station, you should grab it and fill up your tank at the yard - it will definitely be more expensive again.
Seasonal and precision farming compatible. For the sake of realism, the correction of the purchase prices should be deactivated in Revamp.
FS22_DefPack please take the current version min 1.0.0.1 from the Gitlab.

gitHub: https://github.com/s4t4n/FS22_RandomFuelsPrices]]></en>
<fr><![CDATA[Comme dans la vraie vie, le prix du diesel ne cesse de changer, et de temps en temps le prix de l'AdBlue (DEF) aussi.
Si jamais vous obtenez un prix bon marché à la station-service, vous devriez le saisir et faire le plein dans la cour - ce sera certainement encore plus cher.
Compatible avec l'agriculture saisonnière et de précision. Par souci de réalisme, la correction des prix d'achat devrait être désactivée dans Revamp.
FS22_DefPack veuillez prendre la version actuelle au moins 1.0.0.1 du Gitlab.

github : https://github.com/s4t4n/FS22_RandomFuelsPrices]]></fr>
    </description>

    <iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="variprices.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n>
		<text name="text_Dieselpreis">
			<de>Akueller Dieselpreis: </de>
			<en>current diesel price</en>
		</text>
		<text name="text_ElectricalYear">
			<de>Jährlich geänderte Strompreise: </de>
			<en>Annually changing electricity prices</en>
		</text>
		<text name="text_Gaspreis">
			<de>Neue Gaspreise: </de>
			<en>New methane prices</en>
		</text>
		<text name="text_Defpreis">
            <de>Akueller AdBluepreis: </de>
			<en>current def price</en>
        </text>
		<text name="text_DieselpreisNew">
			<de>Preisänderung Diesel: </de>
			<en>diesel price changed</en>
		</text>
		<text name="text_DefpreisNew">
            <de>Preisänderung AdBlue: </de>
			<en>def price changed</en>
        </text>
	</l10n>
	<!-- <dependencies> -->
        <!-- <dependency>FS22_DefPack.zip</dependency> -->
    <!-- </dependencies> -->
</modDesc>
 